{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242422025","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242422024"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" bbbee1f5-8e19-476a-9052-8724f9381e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242422259","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242422258"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" bbbee1f5-8e19-476a-9052-8724f9381e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242423233","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242423232"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" bbbee1f5-8e19-476a-9052-8724f9381e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242424507","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242424506"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" bbbee1f5-8e19-476a-9052-8724f9381e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242427466","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242427465"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" bbbee1f5-8e19-476a-9052-8724f9381e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242428324","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242428323"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" bbbee1f5-8e19-476a-9052-8724f9381e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242428647","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242428647"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" bbbee1f5-8e19-476a-9052-8724f9381e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242429891","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242429891"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" bbbee1f5-8e19-476a-9052-8724f9381e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242433478","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242433478"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" bbbee1f5-8e19-476a-9052-8724f9381e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242434473","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242434473"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" bbbee1f5-8e19-476a-9052-8724f9381e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242434732","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242434731"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" bbbee1f5-8e19-476a-9052-8724f9381e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242435686","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242435686"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" bbbee1f5-8e19-476a-9052-8724f9381e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242438623","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242438622"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" bbbee1f5-8e19-476a-9052-8724f9381e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242439664","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242439663"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" bbbee1f5-8e19-476a-9052-8724f9381e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242440137","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242440137"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" bbbee1f5-8e19-476a-9052-8724f9381e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242441906","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242441905"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" bbbee1f5-8e19-476a-9052-8724f9381e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242441984","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242441984"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" bbbee1f5-8e19-476a-9052-8724f9381e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242465146","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242465146"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242470922","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242470922"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242475965","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242475965"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242500322","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242500322"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242585446","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242585446"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242595550","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242595550"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242599873","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242599873"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242606139","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242606139"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242610025","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242610024"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242616447","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242616447"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242621524","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242621523"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242630847","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242630847"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242635116","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242635116"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242739902","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242739902"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242752308","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242752308"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242757201","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242757201"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242763944","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242763944"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242769276","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242769276"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242774651","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242774651"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242780412","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242780412"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242785193","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242785193"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242788910","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242788910"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242793546","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242793546"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242798046","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242798046"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242803305","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242803305"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242808604","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242808604"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242855610","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242855610"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 29c3c51f-2fb4-4736-b9a9-fd0222a4095a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242889594","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242889594"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 92980235-108b-4921-bdf3-ece72d81ee9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_11-6-14"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 14"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242970523","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242970522"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 92980235-108b-4921-bdf3-ece72d81ee9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_6_11-6-14"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242985025","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242985024"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 92980235-108b-4921-bdf3-ece72d81ee9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_6_11-6-14"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550242992850","data":{"timestamp":" 1550242992850"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 92980235-108b-4921-bdf3-ece72d81ee9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_6_11-6-14"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243003118","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243003118"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" a3915d09-8779-4145-b2c9-ae77a4fe44c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243008491","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243008491"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" a3915d09-8779-4145-b2c9-ae77a4fe44c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243013373","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243013373"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" a3915d09-8779-4145-b2c9-ae77a4fe44c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243022235","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243022234"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" a3915d09-8779-4145-b2c9-ae77a4fe44c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243027873","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243027873"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" a3915d09-8779-4145-b2c9-ae77a4fe44c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243033156","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243033155"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" a3915d09-8779-4145-b2c9-ae77a4fe44c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243037211","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243037211"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" a3915d09-8779-4145-b2c9-ae77a4fe44c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243040946","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243040945"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" a3915d09-8779-4145-b2c9-ae77a4fe44c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243045292","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243045291"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" a3915d09-8779-4145-b2c9-ae77a4fe44c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243046721","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243046720"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" a3915d09-8779-4145-b2c9-ae77a4fe44c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243053771","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243053770"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" a3915d09-8779-4145-b2c9-ae77a4fe44c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243060233","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243060233"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" a3915d09-8779-4145-b2c9-ae77a4fe44c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243067722","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243067721"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" a3915d09-8779-4145-b2c9-ae77a4fe44c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243078567","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243078567"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 7c4bd803-f279-47ce-aab7-806d95dc321c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243081576","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243081576"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 7c4bd803-f279-47ce-aab7-806d95dc321c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243090129","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243090129"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 7c4bd803-f279-47ce-aab7-806d95dc321c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243094841","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243094841"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 7c4bd803-f279-47ce-aab7-806d95dc321c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243101148","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243101148"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 7c4bd803-f279-47ce-aab7-806d95dc321c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243107217","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243107217"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 7c4bd803-f279-47ce-aab7-806d95dc321c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243110676","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243110676"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 7c4bd803-f279-47ce-aab7-806d95dc321c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243116196","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243116196"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 7c4bd803-f279-47ce-aab7-806d95dc321c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243119529","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243119529"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 7c4bd803-f279-47ce-aab7-806d95dc321c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243123544","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243123543"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 7c4bd803-f279-47ce-aab7-806d95dc321c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243128926","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243128926"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 7c4bd803-f279-47ce-aab7-806d95dc321c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243132154","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243132153"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 7c4bd803-f279-47ce-aab7-806d95dc321c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243137606","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243137606"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 7c4bd803-f279-47ce-aab7-806d95dc321c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243142998","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243142998"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 7c4bd803-f279-47ce-aab7-806d95dc321c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243150574","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243150574"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 7c4bd803-f279-47ce-aab7-806d95dc321c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243158261","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243158261"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 7c4bd803-f279-47ce-aab7-806d95dc321c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243166918","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243166918"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 7c4bd803-f279-47ce-aab7-806d95dc321c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243176012","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243176012"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 12b40fa9-a156-4d55-9459-549a189db952"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243178082","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243178082"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 12b40fa9-a156-4d55-9459-549a189db952"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243178106","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243178106"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 12b40fa9-a156-4d55-9459-549a189db952"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243178194","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243178193"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 12b40fa9-a156-4d55-9459-549a189db952"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243184865","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243184864"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 12b40fa9-a156-4d55-9459-549a189db952"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243192231","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243192230"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 12b40fa9-a156-4d55-9459-549a189db952"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243199898","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243199898"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 12b40fa9-a156-4d55-9459-549a189db952"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243231723","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243231722"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" e2d8f54c-919f-4fa9-bdc5-3dd83f2109af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_d-o-i"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243240135","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243240135"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" e2d8f54c-919f-4fa9-bdc5-3dd83f2109af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_d-o-i"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243244378","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243244378"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" e2d8f54c-919f-4fa9-bdc5-3dd83f2109af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_t-n-o"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243256271","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243256271"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" e2d8f54c-919f-4fa9-bdc5-3dd83f2109af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_t-n-o"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243260004","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243260004"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" e2d8f54c-919f-4fa9-bdc5-3dd83f2109af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_r-k-o"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243263464","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243263464"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" e2d8f54c-919f-4fa9-bdc5-3dd83f2109af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_g-i-o"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243272249","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243272249"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" e2d8f54c-919f-4fa9-bdc5-3dd83f2109af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-g-y"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243273645","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243273645"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" e2d8f54c-919f-4fa9-bdc5-3dd83f2109af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-g-y"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243288531","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243288531"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" cfa14c98-fffe-4706-b2a3-9eaac3e7f5bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_b-h-o"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243289237","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243289236"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" cfa14c98-fffe-4706-b2a3-9eaac3e7f5bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_o_b-h-o"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243312447","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243312447"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" cfa14c98-fffe-4706-b2a3-9eaac3e7f5bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_o_b-h-o"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243322004","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243322004"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 0102addb-30e4-4612-a67e-12529e0b61be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_f-o-i"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243328550","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243328550"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 0102addb-30e4-4612-a67e-12529e0b61be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_f-o-i"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243334088","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243334088"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 0102addb-30e4-4612-a67e-12529e0b61be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_f-o-i"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243337532","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243337532"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 0102addb-30e4-4612-a67e-12529e0b61be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_t-n-o"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243342742","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243342741"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 0102addb-30e4-4612-a67e-12529e0b61be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_r-k-o"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243346153","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243346153"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 0102addb-30e4-4612-a67e-12529e0b61be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_d-o-i"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243353101","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243353100"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 0102addb-30e4-4612-a67e-12529e0b61be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_d-o-i"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243363466","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243363465"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 0102addb-30e4-4612-a67e-12529e0b61be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_d-o-i"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243367310","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243367310"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 0102addb-30e4-4612-a67e-12529e0b61be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_b-h-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243373286","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243373286"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 0102addb-30e4-4612-a67e-12529e0b61be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_b-h-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243375414","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243375414"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 0102addb-30e4-4612-a67e-12529e0b61be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_o_b-h-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243387083","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243387082"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 0102addb-30e4-4612-a67e-12529e0b61be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_o_b-h-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550243395619","data":{"timestamp":" 1550243395619"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_175332"," gameId":" 0102addb-30e4-4612-a67e-12529e0b61be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.107"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_o_b-h-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}